

BISHESH SUNAM

27 YEARS OLD SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



Address. 59 View rd, Mt.Eden Auckland



Phone. 022-4050-486



Email.bishesh.sunam@gmail.com

PROFILE

A professional enthusiastic person expertise in building professional websites, desktop applications, games, software, and more.

Passionate and motivated, who is always willing to take extra miles to overcome new challenges as a Professional Software Developer.

MY SKILLS

PROFESSINAL SKILLS

- · JavaScript, C#, Python
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, ReactJs, NextJs
- · MongoDb, SQL Server, Firestore
- · Selenium, Katalon Studio
- npm, GitHub, docker, kubernetes
- Heroku, Google Cloud Platform, Vercel, AWS

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Team Work
- Leadership
- Integrity
- Loyalty

REFERENCE

Daryl George (Business Analyst) Coca Cola Amatil , Auckland darylgeorge646@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE



Software Developer

ASPIRE2., JAN, 2020 - JUN, 2020

- Working with the wider development team.
- Maintain an understanding of current web technologies or programming practices through continuing education, reading, or participation in professional conferences, workshops, or groups.
- Use and maintain software on version control systems such as Git Hub



Data Admin

LAZYAZ LTD., 2017 - 2018

- Answer user inquiries regarding computer software or hardware operation to resolve problems.
- Maintain records of daily data communication transactions, problems and remedial actions taken, or installation activities.
- Monitored and administered back-end websites and related software to coordinate with the supply chain.
- Providing desktop service/ attending phone calls for instruction of using application and websites.

EDUCATION



Bachelor of Computing Systems

UNITEC, 2019 - 2022

Academic Excellence in software design and develop



Diploma in Computing level 5,6 & 7

NTEC, 2014 - 2019

 Academic Excellence in Product Design & develop